petforums.co.uk 2019-12-24

# Privacy Policy | Pet Forums Community

###  __ Welcome to PetForums

Join thousands of other pet owners and pet lovers on the UK's most popular and friendly pet community and discussion forum. 

We are "Pet Forums Community", the UKs most popular pet community and forum platform provided via this website (petforums.co.uk and its subdomains). PetForums is the trading name of Pet Media Ltd, a registered company (Number 06696819) in England and Wales. Our registered address is 4 Old Park Lane, Mayfair, London, W1K 1QW.

At "Pet Forums Community", we recognise that the privacy of your personal information is very important and we are committed to respecting and protecting your privacy.

This privacy policy explains how we “Pet Forums Community” (Petforums.co.uk and its subdomains) collects, uses and protects any information that you give when you use our services and under which conditions we may disclose it to others.

Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using our services, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy policy for the purpose of providing our services to you.

PetForums may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. By using our website and other services, you are agreeing to be bound by this policy and our terms of use which form part of this privacy policy.

Pet Media Ltd is the data controller and operator of the Petforums website and apps. If you have any questions regarding this policy or our practices, you can contact us by using our contact us page or by writing to us at Pet Forums Community, Pet Media Ltd, 4 Old Park Lane, Mayfair, London, W1K 1QW.

## What information we hold about you

The type of data that we collect and process includes:

  * Your name or username.
  * Your email address.
  * Your IP address.

Further data may be collected if you choose to share it, such as if you fill out fields on your profile.

We collect some or all of this information in the following cases:

  * You register as a member on this site.
  * You fill out our contact form.
  * You browse this site. See "Cookie policy" below.
  * You fill out fields on your profile.

## How your personal information is used

We may use your personal information in the following ways:

  * For the purposes of making you a registered member of our site, in order for you to contribute content to this site.
  * We may use your email address to inform you of activity on our site.
  * Your IP address is recorded when you perform certain actions on our site. Your IP address is never publicly visible.

## Other ways we may use your personal information.

In addition to notifying you of activity on our site which may be relevant to you, from time to time we may wish to communicate with all members any important information such as newsletters or announcements by email. You can opt-in to or opt-out of such emails in your profile.

We may collect non-personally identifiable information about you in the course of your interaction with our site. This information may include technical information about the browser or type of device you're using. This information will be used purely for the purposes of analytics and tracking the number of visitors to our site.

## Keeping your data secure

We are committed to ensuring that any information you provide to us is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable measures and procedures to safeguard and secure the information that we collect.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

## Cookie policy

Cookies are small text files which are set by us on your computer which allow us to provide certain functionality on our site, such as being able to log in, or remembering certain preferences.

We have a detailed cookie policy and more information about the cookies that we set on this page.

## Rights

You have a right to access the personal data we hold about you or obtain a copy of it. To do so please contact us. If you believe that the information we hold for you is incomplete or inaccurate, you may contact us to ask us to complete or correct that information.

You also have the right to request the erasure of your personal data. Please contact us if you would like us to remove your personal data.

## Acceptance of this policy

Continued use of our site signifies your acceptance of this policy. If you do not accept the policy then please do not use this site. When registering we will further request your explicit acceptance of the privacy policy.

## Changes to this policy

We may make changes to this policy at any time. You may be asked to review and re-accept the information in this policy if it changes in the future.
